Okay, so this is the bodysuit. Fun fact, you can remove this front shield here because these buckles are fully functional. And then you can wear pasties underneath because pasties are actually part of this outfit.
I kinda love sporty bags.
But I also like the design from the front because we have a lot going on here.
Again we have these reflective stripes, it's again a tactical design.
We have these criss-cross stripes here.
And there is actually a zipper in the front I can completely open.
So whoops, which I did.
You actually have to open the zipper and these buckles to get into it.
I also like the design here with the fake straps and the little collar.
There are no snaps in the crotch area so slight minus point every time you have to go to the
toilet you have to completely undress or just, I don't know, pull it to the side.
Alright and now for the last outfit.
This fun bodysuit.
And here we go.
I actually am going to get rid of the shoes because the stay ups are really slippery
and I'm sliding around in the heels.
Much better this way. I think the design is very very bright and fun.
I think it looks very good also with the design again and the cut here.
So it makes a high waist optically, visually and it's a fun design.
So...
I think this would be a great outfit for streaming for example.
I actually wanted to start streaming on Twitch a while ago, but I just didn't manage it this year.
There was so much else going on, but if you have any recommendations for good games
write it down in the comments and maybe I'll find a time next year to do a twitch stream
but yeah this is kind of an outfit I would see myself behind my laptop and just gaming away
looks like an e-girl outfit so I wouldn't call this a cosplay but I think it's a very fun and
and yeah, dynamic. It's a very fun and dynamic outfit with the stripes and it looks almost a bit like a racing suit or I don't know, swimsuit, something dynamic anyway.
Maybe I should start posing with the chair.
Would actually be a nice picture from what I can see in the mirror. I can turn around.
Anyway, what I wanted to say as well is that the shipping was really fast so if you want
to order there it was at my place within a week.
And yeah, as I said check out the webstore.
Thanks again Mr. Jay Koss for sending me these outfits.
I really enjoyed trying something different especially this bodysuit and also the white
and blue outfit.
So I'm really happy with how it's turned out. I don't know what my favorite is actually. I kind of like this the most maybe but it's also my style, my usual style. So maybe I'm biased. I'm definitely biased. Anyway I hope you're having a nice day and check out my other videos, my socials and leave a thumbs up. Subscribe to my channel. I will see you in the next video. Bye.